apartmentonline.com 2003-04-02

# All About Roommates - Our Privacy Statement

AllAboutRoommates.com is a roommate locator service provided by Rent and Sell, Inc. 

To report any abuse or violations of the All About Roommates service, please send email to abuse@AllAboutRoommates.com and attach an unedited copy of the email message that you feel was sent to you in error or without your permission. Include all header information so that we can trace origin of the message. Also include any notes or other information that you feel are pertinent. Any questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy may be directed to privacy@AllAboutRoommates.com. 

**Web Site Information Collection**  
For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes only the consumer's domain name or IP address, but not the e-mail address. Unless otherwise stated on our web site, we collect only the domain name or IP address of visitors to our Web page, the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, the e-mail addresses of those who make postings to our directory, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, user-specific information on what pages consumers access or visit, information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and registrations to access portions of the site and their related services or to set up an All About Roommates account. We also collect click stream information. We use Authorize Net's SSL (secure socket layer) encryption for online payment collection for purchases of our own proprietary products and services, which includes the All About Roommates roommate directory and email service. We rely on third party providers for some of our products and services which may be advertised via the All About Roommates service–the privacy policies of those sites govern the method by which they collect and use such information.

**Use of Web Site Information Collected**  
The information we collect is used to create an aggregate demographic profile of our user base so that we can improve the content and services of our Web site and provide aggregate information to potential advertisers (no individual information is provided to any third-party without your consent), to customize the content and/or layout of our page for each individual visitor, to notify consumers about updates to our Web site and services, to send visitors our opt-in e-mail newsletter(s) (if requested by the visitor), to provide users with the products and/or services for which they signed-up or registered which may include sending service disruption notices or other service- or product-related information via e-mail, and is not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes without the visitor's consent. We may share collected information with another company in the event that we merge with or are acquired by another company. Customers may prevent their information from being used for purposes other than those for which it was originally collected by sending us e-mail at the above address. Upon request we provide site visitors with access to contact information (e.g., name, address, phone number) that we maintain about them. You can access this information, and/or have it corrected, by logging into your account online.

**E-mail and Direct Response Contact  
**All of our direct response methods are opt-in. If you subscribed to our roommate locator service(s) but do not want to receive future service, please follow the "deactivate" instructions available in the "manage account" under member login.

Third-Party Opt-In E-mail: If you opted into our "third-party" services (such as but not limited to moving resources and background screening resources), your e-mail may be made available to other organizations whose products or services you might find interesting. If you do not want your e-mail address to be shared with other companies or organizations, please do not opt into this e-mail services when asked this question. If you opted into this list(s) and want to opt out, follow the instructions on the e-mail that is sent to you to "Unsubscribe" to that list(s).

**Postal Address Collection and Use  
**If you supply us with your postal address on-line, we will use it to send you the information for which you provided us your address. If you supply us with your telephone number on-line, we will use it to contact you with information regarding your account, orders you have placed, or with information regarding your inquiry. We may send you information about additional services that we offer, but we will not rent or sell your contact information to any third parties without your permission.

**Cookies  
**We, and some of our partners who provide some of the services and products on our site, use cookies to record session information, such as items that consumers add to their shopping cart, record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, record past activity at a site in order to provide better service when visitors return to our site, customize Web page content based on visitors' browser type or other information that the visitor sends, and to enable access to specific areas on the web site.

**Ad Servers and Other Partners**  
To try and bring you offers, that may be of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads or provide other services or products on our Web pages, our e-mail newsletter(s), and other services. As a result of your visit to our site, these companies may collect non-personally-identifiable information such as your domain type, your IP address and click stream information. For further information, consult the privacy policies of the advertisers or partners.

**Children's Guidelines  
**This website is directed at adults, not children, and we do not seek to collect from children online contact information or distribution to third parties any personally identifiable information from children or entice children to divulge information to us.

**Security  
**When we transfer and receive certain types of sensitive information such as financial information, we redirect visitors to a secure. We strive to maintain appropriate security measures in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site. Although we take reasonable measures to secure our data, we cannot guarantee that the measures we take are or will remain adequate. Some portions of our sites and services link to other companies' web sites. Please refer to the privacy policies of those sites for information on how they handle security for information they collect.

**Changes to Privacy Policy**  
From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in this Privacy Policy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future, we will post the policy changes to our Web site's Privacy Policy page to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site's Privacy Policy page periodically.

Last Update: May-1-2002

AllAboutRoommates.com is a product of Rent and Sell, Inc.

Copyright © 2002 Rent and Sell, Inc. All rights reserved.

* * *
